## **OBJECTIVE**

Self-motivated, energetic and Collaborative mobile application developer with a four-year track record in designing the user interface and developing the mobile applications. Devoted individual with in-depth knowledge consisting of mobile development technologies along with user design principles. Looking to grow within an organization and continue to expand my knowledge and skill set.

# **SKILLS**

### Flutter Stack

Dart, Sate Mgmt Block | Freezed, Dio, Hive, Unit & Integration tests, Dart to Native, Plugins

#### iOS Stack

Swift, URL Sessions, Alamofire, Core Data, UIKit, Application lifecycle, Remote notifications, Background modes, Location tracking

## **EXPERIENCE**

### FLUTTER DEVELOPER • FIRST UKRAINIAN BANK • 10/2021 - PRESENT

- Improved the current version of the mobile banking application by developing and deploying an alternate authentication method such as face recognition.
- Fully understanding the entire SDLC Process and engaging the needed parties throughout the SDLC process.
- Communicated with back-end engineers, system analysists, designers and marketers.
- Simplified technical industry jargon into a simplistic form while ensuring that the team in its entirety understands both the technical and business requirements.
- Analyzed and reviewed application code.

### **FLUTTER DEVELOPER • ADRAS • 09/2020 - 10/2021**

- Created and developed an application into a scalable cross-platform application.
- During the development lifecycle, engaged other teams on app architecture, state management, networking and decision making with SMEs.
- Implemented and deployed application releases with Firebase distribution, Fast Lane, and GitHub actions.
- Paired Flutter with C++ library via Dart foreign function interface.

### **IOS DEVELOPER • MOBINDUSTRY • 09/2018 - 09/2020**

- Developed an intuitive user interface for an e-commerce site ensuring that the user interface is easy to interact with and provides the best possible experience.
- Developed comments and reviews and embedded this directly into the ecommerce site creating the functionality allowed the end user to leave a YouTube video directly on the e-commerce site.
- Gained a level if understanding in regards to legacy code such as OBJ C.

# **EDUCATION**

MASTERS DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE • UKRAINIAN STATE UNIVERSITY • 2018

BACHELORS DEGREE IN CIVIL ENGINEERING • PSACEA • 2016